Paul Bigelow Sears Collection, 1832-1969 (bulk 1930-1966) MS 455
University of Arizona
- Series III: Research Files
  - Subseries 5: People, 1911-1959
    - Kapp, R. O., undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Kezerian, Stephen, 1952 (Box 6, File 47)
    - Lawrence and Elson, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Lawrence, Donald B., undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Leopold, Estella B., undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Lyon, Charles J., 1935 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - MacClintock, Paul, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Martin, Paul S., undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Parsons, Elsie Clews, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Potter, L., undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Ralska, M., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Smiley, Terah L., undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Smith, C. C., undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Smith, E. R., undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Smith, John B., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Smith, Preston, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Taber, Stephen, undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Terra, Helmut de, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Thomas, H. H., undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Tsukada, Matsuo, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Wells, B. W., undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Wendorf, Fred, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Whitaker, Thomas, Cutter, Hugh C. and MacNeish, Richard S., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Whitton, E. S., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Wilcox, Arthur N., undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Wilson, L. R., 1945-1963 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Winder, C. G., undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Wright, H. E., undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Zimmermann, Prof. Dr., undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Subseries 6: Field Notes, 1916-1961
    - 1916-1919 - Logs (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - 1921 – Logs (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - 1925 – Logs (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - 1926-1928 – Logs (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - 1927-1929 – Pollen (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - 1928-1930 – Logs (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - 1930 – Logs (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - 1930-1965 – Peat Collections (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Untitled (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - 1931-1933 – Logs (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 1934 – Logs (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 1935 – Logs (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 1936-1941 – Pollen Analysis (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 1938 – Logs (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 1942-1948 – Mexico Core Notes (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 1946-1947 – Logs (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 1948 – Logs (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 1948 – Mexican Pollen Counts (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 1948 – Peat Log – Mexico (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 1948-1955 – Fossil Pollen Collections (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 1950-1953 – Logs (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 1953 – Castalia – Techniques – Logs (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 1953 – Logs (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 1955-1960 – Procedure Records (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - 1956 – Herbarium Records (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 1956 – Notes on Pollen Structure (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - 1956-1960- Michellinda – Miscellaneous Notes (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - 1959 – Logs (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - 1959 – Pollen Samples At Gibbs (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - 1961 – Logs (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Logs – Castalia, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)